(Sheldon:)You know, the more
I think about it,
(Sheldon:)the more intrigued I am
about having our own store.
(Howard:)We'll get to see
all the new stuff
(Howard:)before it hits the shelves.
(Sheldon:)And we'll get to have
fun interactions
(Sheldon:)with our customers.
"This isn't a library--
buy it or get out."
(Howard:)You say things like that
all the time.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but as a store owner,
I'll finally have
a good comeback
to, "You don't work here--
shut up."
(Leonard:)Uh, do you know how Penny
told Raj he should have
(Leonard:)left her off his list?
Yeah.
(Leonard:)Well, do you think when she
and I had that conversation,
she left people off her list?
(Sheldon:)I'm sure she did.
(Leonard:)Why?
(Sheldon:)Because if she hadn't,
(Sheldon:)she'd still be wading
through the list.
(Leonard:)Will you stay out of this?
(chuckles) If only Penny
had said that once in a while.
(Howard:)Hey, what difference
does it make?
(Howard:)You're the one
she wants to marry.
(Leonard:)That's true.
Yeah, and I'm not sure
(Howard:)that complete honesty
is always the best thing